

PROFILE INFO -

A highly-skilled and creative Digital Marketing Expert with 2+ years of experience in developing and executing digital marketing campaigns, SEO optimization, and social media management.

Possesses excellent digital marketing strategy and campaign creation, content writing, and analytics skills. Proven track record of increasing website traffic and sales conversion rates.

EDMUND MWANJELLE

COMM & DIGITAL MARKETING EXPERT



PHONE

+254 727 169 210



EMAIL

edmundofficial@gmail.com



ADDRESS Meru, Kenya.



MY SKILLS

- Digital marketing tactics
- SEO, SEM, & content marketing
- Professional Email design
- Google & Web Analytics tools
- Social media expert
- Web development
- Communication skills
- Creative problem-solving skills

LANGUAGE SKILLS

English 95%
Kiswahili 99%

WORK EXPERIENCE •

FEB 2022 DEC 2022

DIGITAL MARKETING EXPERT

EMERALD LOUNGE AND CHOMA ZONE

- * Designing mail templates for lounge
- * Creating and Pushing e-posters
- * Developing Marketing Reports
- * Working closely with the Manager
- * Coming up with marketing strategies

MAR 2021 JAN 2022

DIGITAL MARKETING EXPERT

PARAMOUNT & WESTWIND HOTELS

- * Designing mail templates for hotels
- * Sending and monitoring emails
- * Creating and Pushing e-posters
- * Developing Marketing Reports
- * Working closely with Marketing Manager
- * Coming up with marketing strategies

REFERENCE

CATHERINE NKANACI

MERU PARAMOUNT HOTEL - MARKETER 254 722 991 642

PETER MUTHENGI

EMERALD LOUNGE - MANAGER 254 720 419 479

MY EDUCATION —

JAN 2020

DIGITAL MARKETINGAJIRA DIGITAL

AUG 2015

DIP IN MULTIMEDIA DEVELOPMENTALISON.COM

CURRICULUM VITAE

PERSONAL INFORMATION:

NAME : Edmund Mwanjelle

GENDER : Male

DATE OF BIRTH : 09-02-1989
RELIGION : Christian
NATIONALITY : Kenyan
ID NUMBER : 27336556

ADDRESS : Mlondo Primary School

P.O Box 39- 80308

Sagalla – Voi

CELL PHONE : +254 727 169210 or +254 798 064 149

EMAIL : <u>edmundofficial@gmail.com</u>

PROFILE:

I am authoritative, multi-talented, and self-motivated person. I am also charismatic and God fearing.

EDUCATION:

- 1. Diploma in Mastering Business Skills Trace Academia December 2022
- 2. Understanding Research Methods and Approaches (www.alison.com) August 2021
- 3. Financial Sales Generation Kenya July 2019 August 2019
- 4. Diploma in Project Management at (www.alison.com) 2015 to 2016
- 5. Diploma in Multimedia Development at (www.alison.com) 2014 2015
- 6. Diploma in Journalism and Mass Communication Intraglobal Training Institute, Nairobi, Kenya 2008-2009
- 7. Mwambiti Secondary School, Sagalla, Taita Taveta County. (KCSE-KNEC) 2004-2007
- 8. Mlondo Primary School, Sagalla, Taita Taveta County. (KCPE-KNEC) 1995-2003

SHORT COURSES:

- Emergency planning July 2019
 Humanitarian Leadership Academy www.kayaconnect.org
- Introduction to Child Protection February 2019
 Humanitarian Leadership Academy
 www.kayaconnect.org
- 3. Information Security February 2019 Humanitarian Leadership Academy www.kayaconnect.org

EXPERIENCE:

Media Director

- Team Leader

GGV F	FM (Vispat Communication Network) – March 10 th to date:
	Head of Radio
-	Maintaining and overseeing daily programming Managing day-day operations
-	Actively participating in defining short and long team goals
-	Providing support for senior station management
GGV F	FM (Vispat Communication Network) – November 29 th 2019 to date.
	Head of News Department
-	Assign reporters tasks
-	Edit News before broadcast
-	Read prime time news
Pione	er Insurance Company Ltd - September 2 nd 2019 to date
	Sales Advisor
	- Sale different insurance products to qualified prospects
Sifa F	M Stations Limited, Voi, Kenya - January 2010 to date
	Presenter/Producer - News editor and Senior Reporter
	- Prepare and anchor prime time news, 7.00pm and 9.00pm
	- Head of sports department
	 Host late-night adult show (9.00pm – 12.00am) Monday to Saturday Produce pre-recorded programs
	- Teach students who are in Industrial Attachments basic reporting and news writing skills
Africa 2015	n Media and Film Development, AMFID, Voi, Kenya – December 2014 to September

- Shoot and produce videos
- Packaging and storage of videos

Miss Tourism Kenya Taita Taveta, Kenya- July 2013 to January 2014

□ Voi Coordinator

- Coordinate all events in Voi
- Distribute posters and fliers
- Frequently contact participants and give them updates from Nairobi office

OTHER SKILLS:

Computer programming: HTML and CSS, Python, Java, Currently learning Java Script and jQuery.
Computer Maintenance (both hardware and software), Networking, Web Designing and Graphics
Video & Audio Production
Photography
Trained on Human Rights and Conflict reporting by Media Council of Kenya
Trained on sensitive reporting by Media Focus on Africa.
Trained on Women and Child reporting by Media Diversity
Trained on Social Media Reporting by Internews Kenya
Trained as a Social Media Activist by Human Rights Agenda
Trained as a Paralegal by Kituo Cha Sheria

INTERESTS AND HOBBIES:

I live right by socializing, reading magazines and newspaper, adventure, videography and photography. Since I was young, I developed an interest in technology. I like playing Volleyball, walking race and table tennis

REFEREES

1) Edgar Kalimbo Station Manager Sifa 107.7FM Cell phone No. 0725 890 743

Fred MrambaInstructorGeneration Kenya – VoiCell phone No. 0788 99444

3) Bishop Patrick Kariuki Chairman

Vispat Communication Network Cell Phone No. 0722 882 382